So, UKIP, the UK Independence Party,
Nigel Farage's former political party,
just unveiled its new uh logo. And when
my colleague Jack revealed this to me,
my colleague Georgia joked, "Haha, is it
is it a swastika?" And then he turned
his phone around and no, but close
enough. Um, look, and I know that
they're kind of doing this uh partly to
signal to fellow far-right people uh
that if you also uh think that the wrong
side lost in World War II, come and join
our party. And I know they're also
partly doing it uh just to raise
controversy so that we all talk about
it. And this is sort of playing into
that. But I am so tired. So I think as
much as any particular like political uh
ideal, one of the things that really
irks me in in trying to do this job is
is kind of like like and and
my like level for that is people uh
using statistics slightly wrong or like
making disingenuine arguments. Um and
the fact that then we also have to sort
of deal with this kind of stuff.
I'm so tired.